samsara.com 2015-10-09

# Samsara Privacy Policy

                                Samsara Privacy Policy
                                     Last Updated: 7/21/2015
Protecting your privacy is really important to us. With this in mind, we’re providing this Privacy
Policy to explain our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that we
receive through our Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third-party websites,
services or applications, even if they are accessible through our Services. Also, please note that,
unless we define a term in this Privacy Policy, all capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy have
the same meanings as in our Terms of Service. So, please make sure that you have read and
understand our Terms of Service.
Revisions to this Privacy Policy
Any information that is collected via our Services is covered by the Privacy Policy in effect at the
time such information is collected. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make
any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we’ll notify you of those changes by posting them on
the Services or by sending you an email or other notification, and we’ll update the “Last Updated
Date” above to indicate when those changes will become effective.
Collection and Use of Information
Information Collected or Received from You
Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Services, to administer
your use of the Services (including your Account, if you are an Account holder), and to enable you
to enjoy and easily navigate our Services.
Account Information. If you create an Account, we’ll collect certain information that can be used
to identify you, such as your name, email address, postal address, and phone number (“PII”). If
you create an Account using your login credentials from one of your SNS Accounts, we’ll be able
to access and collect your name and email address and other PII that your privacy settings on the
SNS Account permit us to access, which may include your gender, date of birth and other
information that is not considered PII because it cannot be used by itself to identify you..
Information Collected Using Cookies and other Web Technologies. Like many website owners
and operators, we use automated data collection tools such as Cookies and Web Beacons to
collect certain information.
“Cookies” are small text files that are placed on your hard drive by a Web server when you
access our Services. We may use both session Cookies and persistent Cookies to identify that
you’ve logged in to the Services and to tell us how and when you interact with our Services. We
may also use Cookies to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on our Services and to
customize and improve our Services. Unlike persistent Cookies, session Cookies are deleted
when you log off from the Services and close your browser. Although most browsers
automatically accept Cookies, you can change your browser options to stop automatically
accepting Cookies or to prompt you before accepting Cookies. Please note, however, that if you
don’t accept Cookies, you may not be able to access all portions or features of the Services.
Some third-party services providers that we engage (including third-party advertisers) may also
place their own Cookies on your hard drive. Note that this Privacy Policy covers only our use of
Cookies and does not include use of Cookies by such third parties.
“Web Beacons” (also known as Web bugs, pixel tags or clear GIFs) are tiny graphics with a
unique identifier that may be included on our Services for several purposes, including to deliver or

communicate with Cookies, to track and measure the performance of our Services, to monitor
how many visitors view our Services, and to monitor the effectiveness of our advertising. Unlike
Cookies, which are stored on the user’s hard drive, Web Beacons are typically embedded invisibly
on web pages (or in an e-mail).
Information Related to Use of the Services. Our servers automatically record certain information
about how a person uses our Services (we refer to this information as “Log Data”), including both
Account holders and non-Account holders (either, a “User”). Log Data may include information
such as a User’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, operating system, the web page
that a User was visiting before accessing our Services, the pages or features of our Services to
which a User browsed and the time spent on those pages or features, search terms, the links on
our Services that a User clicked on and other statistics. We use Log Data to administer the
Services and we analyze (and may engage third parties to analyze) Log Data to improve,
customize and enhance our Services by expanding their features and functionality and tailoring
them to our Users’ needs and preferences. We may use a person’s IP address to generate
aggregate, non-identifying information about how our Services are used.
Information Sent by Your Mobile Device. We collect certain information that your mobile device
sends when you use our Services, like a device identifier, user settings and the operating system
of your device, as well as information about your use of our Services.
Location Information. When you use our Services, we may collect and store information about
your location by converting your IP address into a rough geo-location or by accessing your mobile
device’s GPS coordinates or coarse location if you enable location services on your device. We
may use location information to improve and personalize our Services for you. If you do not want
us to collect location information, you may disable that feature on your mobile device.
Information that We Share with Third Parties
We will not share any PII that we have collected from or regarding you except as described below:
Information Shared with Our Services Providers. We may engage third-party services providers to
work with us to administer and provide the Services. These third-party services providers have
access to your PII only for the purpose of performing services on our behalf.
Information Shared with Third Parties. We may share aggregated information and non-identifying
information with third parties for industry research and analysis, demographic profiling and other
similar purposes. We utilize Google Analytics, a service provided by Google, Inc. that we use to
gather information about how Users engage with our Site and Services. For more information
about Google Analytics, please visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. We also use
Hubspot to provide us with analytics data regarding users’ interactions with our Services. Users
may opt out by visiting http://www.hubspot.com/legal/privacy-policy.
Information Disclosed in Connection with Business Transactions. Information that we collect from
our users, including PII, is considered to be a business asset. Thus, if we are acquired by a third
party as a result of a transaction such as a merger, acquisition or asset sale or if our assets are
acquired by a third party in the event we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, some or all of
our assets, including your PII, may be disclosed or transferred to a third party acquirer in
connection with the transaction.
Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others. We cooperate with
government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law.

We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private
parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate: (i) to respond to claims,
legal process (including subpoenas); (ii) to protect our property, rights and safety and the
property, rights and safety of a third party or the public in general; and (iii) to stop any activity that
we consider illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.
Your Choices
We offer you choices regarding the collection, use and sharing of your PII and we’ll respect the
choices you make. Please note that if you decide not to provide us with the PII that we request,
you may not be able to access all of the features of the Services.
Opt-Out. We may periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote our
Services. When you receive such promotional communications from us, you will have the
opportunity to “opt-out” (by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you
receive). We do need to send you certain communications regarding the Services and you will not
be able to opt out of those communications – e.g., communications regarding updates to our
Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy or information about billing.
Modifying Your Information. You can access and modify the PII associated with your Account
by submitting a ticket to Samsara Support. If you want us to delete your PII and your Account,
please submit a support ticket with your request. We’ll take steps to delete your information as
soon we can, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as
otherwise required by law.
Responding to Do Not Track Signals
Our Site does not have the capability to respond to “Do Not Track” signals received from various
web browsers.
The Security of Your Information
We take reasonable administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect the
information that we collect from or about you (including your PII) from unauthorized access, use or
disclosure. Please be aware, however, that no method of transmitting information over the
Internet or storing information is completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the
absolute security of any information.
Links to Other Sites
Our Services may contain links to websites and services that are owned or operated by third
parties (each, a “Third-party Service”). Any information that you provide on or to a Third-party
Service or that is collected by a Third-party Service is provided directly to the owner or operator
of the Third-party Service and is subject to the owner’s or operator’s privacy policy. We’re not
responsible for the content, privacy or security practices and policies of any Third-party Service.
To protect your information we recommend that you carefully review the privacy policies of all
Third-party Services that you access.
International Transfer
Your PII may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state,
province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as
protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you’re located outside the United States and choose to
provide your PII to us, we may transfer your PII to the United States and process it there.

Our Policy Toward Children
Our Services are not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect PII from
children under 13. If we learn that we have collected PII of a child under 13 we will take steps to
delete such information from our files as soon as possible.
Questions?
Please contact us at info@sansara.com if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy.
